- Now here "Dancing
In The Streets,"
Martha and the Vandellas.
(audience clapping)
(upbeat music)
♪ Calling out around the world ♪
♪ Are you ready for
a brand new beat? ♪
♪ Summer's here and
the time is right ♪
♪ For dancing in the street ♪
♪ They're dancing in Chicago,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ Down in New Orleans,
♪ In New York City,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ All we need is
music, sweet music ♪
♪ There'll be music everywhere ♪
♪ There'll be swinging and
swaying, and records playing ♪
♪ Dancing in the street ♪
♪ Oh, it doesn't
matter what you wear ♪
♪ Just as long as
you are there ♪
♪ So come on, every
guy, grab a girl ♪
♪ Everywhere around the world ♪
♪ They'll be dancing,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ They're dancing in the
street, dancing in the street ♪
♪ Way down in L.A.,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ Every day, they're
♪ Dancing in the street ♪
♪ Let's form a big, strong
line, dancing in the street ♪
♪ Get in time, we're
dancing in the street ♪
♪ Dancing in the street ♪
♪ Across the ocean blue,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ Me and you, we're
dancing in the street, ♪
♪ Dancing in the street ♪
♪ Come on then, let's dance ♪
♪ With feeling, come
on, let's dance ♪
♪ Hey baby, dancing
in the street ♪
♪ Come on and let's dance,
dancing in the street ♪
♪ Everybody dance
in the street now ♪
♪ Dancing in the street ♪
(audience clapping)